#### Md. Golam Mostafa

Senior Software Engineer (.NET)

Phone: +8801886621899 | Email: gmostafa358@gmail.com | LinkedIn Profile | 46/19 Dogair, Demra, Dhaka-1261, BD

# **Career Summary**

Microsoft Certified Professional (MCP) with 9+ years of experience in designing and implementing financial and enterprise solutions using .NET technologies. Specialized in ERP systems for HR, payroll, inventory, accounting, and CRM. Delivered measurable improvements across healthcare, manufacturing, and textile industries. Participate with Agile teams, optimizing APIs, and delivering scalable solutions that improve operational efficiency and system reliability.

### **Technical Skills**

- Programming Languages: C#, ASP.NET Core, TypeScript, JavaScript, Python
- Frameworks: Angular, ASP.NET MVC, ADO.NET, LINQ, Microservices
- Databases: SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Oracle
- Tools: Azure DevOps, Git, TFS, SonarQube
- Reporting Tools: Crystal Reports, RDLC Reports, VBReport8
- **Development Methodologies:** Agile, Scrum

# **Professional Experience**

Hydrus Digital BD (Hybrid-USA) – Senior Software Engineer – Bangladesh

July 2022 - Present

- Developed healthcare analytics tools (RPO, PMT), reducing data processing time by 30% and enhancing system reliability.
- Designed and optimized APIs, cutting response times by 25% and ensuring seamless data integrations.
- Participate Agile workflows, improving sprint efficiency and streamlining product delivery cycles.
- Enhanced code quality by establishing coding standards, reducing production issues.

# KK Destiny (株式会社デスティニー) – Programmer – Bangladesh

May 2018 – July 2022

- Delivered a lease finance solution, improving payment accuracy and reducing client complaints by 15%.
- Collaborated with Project Manager and Japanese clients to implement highway toll systems, increasing transaction efficiency.
- Optimized SQL queries, reducing response time by 40% across critical systems.

### **General Automation Ltd. – Junior Programmer –**Bangladesh

August 2015 – April 2018

- Developed ASP.NET MVC applications, enhancing user satisfaction by optimizing system performance.
- Created reports using Crystal Reports and RDLC, improving internal reporting efficiency.
- Maintained and updated legacy systems to support new business requirements.

## **Remarkable Projects**

• RPO (Resource Process Optimization):

Developed a tool for validating master drug databases, improving data accuracy. *Technologies:* ASP.NET Core API, Angular, PostgreSQL

• PMT (Project Management Tool):

Designed a system to automate internal issue tracking and recommend packaging improvements,

reducing manual errors.

Technologies: ASP.NET Core API, Angular, PostgreSQL

## • Patients Management System:

An automated system for tracking patient information, diagnoses, prescriptions, and interactions.

Technologies: ASP.NET Core API, Angular, PostgreSQL

#### • Lease Finance Solution:

Built a financial platform for Japanese clients to streamline lease payment processing and agreement management.

Technologies: C#, Spiral API, VBReport8

## • Highway Toll Management Systems:

The project is maintenance of the toll collection systems at the core of expressways extend throughout Japan as major arteries, this expressway network.

Technologies: MVC4, JavaScript, SQL Server, VBReport8 Report, MSSQL

## • Invoice Generation for Highway Toll:

Automated data import and invoice generation for tolls.

Technologies: C#, Windows Forms, VBReport8 Report, MSSOL

## • GAL ERP System:

Delivered an ERP system encompassing payroll, sales, and inventory management, reducing operational costs by 20%.

Technologies: ASP.NET MVC, SQL Server, Crystal Reports

# Attendance, Leave and Payroll Software:

Features for attendance tracking, leave management, and payroll processing..

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET Web, Oracle, SQL Server, Crystal Report

• Others Project: School Management System, BD Citizen Registration in Japan, Chabot's for Patients appointment.

#### Certifications

- Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer (MCSD): 2015 | Transcript Link
- Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA): 2016 | Transcript Link
- Web Development in PHP BASIS Institute of Technology & Management, 2015
- Soft Core Training City Bank Ltd, 2014

#### **Education**

#### • Post Graduate Diploma in ICT

Bangladesh Computer Council, 2017

• Diploma in Enterprise System Analysis and Design (C#)

IDB-BISEW IT Scholarship Project, 2016

• Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

National University – SAFS Business Institute, 2011

# References

### **Ashraf Ishrak**

Team Leader Hydrus Digital BD (Pvt) Ltd Phone: +8801677837508 |

Email:ashraf.ishrak@hydrusdigitalbd.com

#### Md. Nadim Hossain Sonet

IT Consultant Ministry of Finance Phone: +8801715653238 |

Email:mailto:nh.sonet@outlook.com